http://www.foodconnex.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Food Connex
Login
Register
SolutionsSupport & ServicesSuccess StoriesAmerican Homestead Natural Hampshire PorkCamellia FoodsP & G Trading CompanyOcean Waves ProductsCanal Fulton ProvisionsExceptional FoodsE G Emil and SonsTampa Steak CompanyAlex and George MeatsSchaller and WeberIndian Ridge ProvisionsThe Common MarketVincent Giordano CorporationAbout UsPartnersGet a Quote
Search ...
Toll Free:
(833) 366-3266|
Contact Us
SolutionsSupport & ServicesSuccess StoriesAmerican Homestead Natural Hampshire PorkCamellia FoodsP & G Trading CompanyOcean Waves ProductsCanal Fulton ProvisionsExceptional FoodsE G Emil and SonsTampa Steak CompanyAlex and George MeatsSchaller and WeberIndian Ridge ProvisionsThe Common MarketVincent Giordano CorporationAbout UsPartnersGet a Quote
You are here:
Home
/
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY STATEMENT
CAI Software, LLC is committed to protecting your privacy.  This privacy statement explains the personal data that CAI Software, LLC processes and how we collect, use, disclose and transfer your personal data.
Collection of your Personal Information
CAI Software, LLC collects login credentials and other personal information on our website, customer portal, and mobile applications. We collect personally identifiable information, such as your email address, name, home or work address or telephone number.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by CAI Software, LLC. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses.
Use of your Personal Information
CAI Software, LLC collects and uses your personal information to deliver the services you have requested. CAI Software, LLC does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties and does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
CAI Software, LLC will disclose your personal information, without notice, only with your consent or if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of CAI Software, LLC and/or its customers; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users, or the public.  Additionally, in the event of a merger, sale, or reorganization, we may transfer any and all personal information we collect to the relevant third party.
Use of Cookies
The CAI Software, LLC web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features.
Changes to this Statement
CAI Software, LLC may occasionally update this Privacy Statement.
Contact Information
If you have any comments or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact www.caisoft.com at .
Signup For Updates Signup with your email address to receive Food Connex's news and updates
Optional email address
Subscribe
About
Us
Food Connex® is cloud-based software for food distributors and processors looking to improve their productivity and profitability. Food Connex helps streamline workflow, improve customer service, and reduce costly mistakes. Its easy QuickBooks integration and Order & Inventory Management tools can improve sales, order taking, fulfillment, pricing, invoicing, purchasing, production, traceability and reporting.
Learn More About Us
Watch Our Videos
View Latest News
Contact
Us
Learn more:Call Toll Free at (833) 366-3266 or (833) foodconnex
IMS Software, LLCFood Connex36 Thurber Blvd. Smithfield, RI 02917
End User Agreement
Privacy Policy
Copyright
IMS Software, LLC. All Rights Reserved.
IMS Software, LLC, and its flagship solution Food Connex, are owned by CAI Software, LLC,A leader in on-demand enterprise management systems. Visit caisoft.com to learn more.
